export const data = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How would you describe your mood stability on a typical day?",
      "options": [
        "Stable+0",
        "Occasionally fluctuating+1",
        "Frequently fluctuating+2",
        "Extreme mood swings+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Stable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you experience episodes of elevated mood or energy followed by depressive periods?",
      "options": [
        "No, not at all+0",
        "Occasionally+1",
        "Frequently+1",
        "Yes, regularly+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No, not at all"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you ever been told by others that your behavior during certain periods seems unusual or extreme?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Rarely+1",
        "Sometimes+2",
        "Frequently+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Never"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does your ability to concentrate and make decisions change during mood episodes?",
      "options": [
        "No significant change+0",
        "Slight impairment+1",
        "Moderate impairment+2",
        "Severe impairment+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No significant change"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you engage in impulsive or risky behaviors during elevated mood periods?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Rarely+1",
        "Sometimes+2",
        "Frequently+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Never"
    },
    {
      "question": "How long do your mood episodes typically last?",
      "options": [
        "A few hours+0",
        "Several days+1",
        "Weeks+2",
        "Months+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "A few hours"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you sought professional help or been diagnosed with a mood disorder, such as bipolar disorder?",
      "options": [
        "Yes+0",
        "Considering it+1",
        "No, not yet+2",
        "No, and I don't plan to+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you experienced significant disruptions in your personal or professional life due to mood swings?",
      "options": [
        "No disruptions+0",
        "Slight disruptions+1",
        "Moderate disruptions+2",
        "Severe disruptions+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No disruptions"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you have a family history of mood disorders, including bipolar disorder?",
      "options": [
        "No family history+0",
        "Uncertain+1",
        "Yes, some family history+2",
        "Yes, significant family history+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No family history"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you believe that addressing and managing mood stability is important for overall well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Strongly agree+0",
        "Agree+1",
        "Neutral+2",
        "Disagree+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Strongly agree"
    }
  ]
}
